<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spring Simple Banking Application on Francis Onyishi</title>
    <link>http://example.org/series/spring-simple-banking-application/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spring Simple Banking Application on Francis Onyishi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© francis 2022</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 17:16:21 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/series/spring-simple-banking-application/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Design and Building of a Simple Banking Application II</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/design_and_building_a_simple_banking_application_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 17:16:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/design_and_building_a_simple_banking_application_2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This post is a sequel of part 1 were talked about some design decisions, especially about building without a mainstream DB. This post is primarily on how I spent half of the time developing this app on spring-security 😫🤕. Nonetheless, this gave me a new picture of how spring applications work&amp;hellip;If it hadn&amp;rsquo;t been for this aspect of the application, I might not have learnt about filters and servlets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design and Building of a Simple Banking Application</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/design_and_building_a_simple_banking_application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 23:05:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/design_and_building_a_simple_banking_application/</guid>
      <description>Introduction After a long time away from Java, I needed to write this small application. An interesting feature of this application quote-unquote is that it would be built without a mainstream DB, not even H2 database. This restriction from using already existing DBs largely influenced my design decisions for the application. Here is the finished code
Thoughts and Design&amp;hellip; I had about six endpoints to implement, which are listed below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
